{
    "id": "64484934149e46458b3dc9f2c9ce8dbc",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will be staying here for ……………………… more days.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aafb3e74e9b4f6aa6bf10dbca0f8d1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is junior …………………………… me.",
            "description": "The words junior and senior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6dfdfc22aa5845a1b4011b1c4a4f4b4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "China is ………………………… than India.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "larger",
                "the larger",
                "the largest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d42300d1eeab4bf9b9ea2e868c874cbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………….. than her.",
            "description": "Younger is the comparative form of young. ",
            "answers": [
                "younger",
                "the younger",
                "more young"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "30fda2aafb8241bd8bf6c4525c259477"
        },
        {
            "question": "I gave the kitten …………………………… milk.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "a little",
                "a few",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8109df1b9f6b446d95bf915067635cdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two routes, this is ………………………………",
            "description": "Use the comparative form when a group consists of just two people or things. ",
            "answers": [
                "short",
                "the shorter",
                "the shortest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ce03d8048464286aea9cdcb6f2a1d1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We got ……………………………….. rain this year. The crops are all dying.",
            "description": "Little means hardly any.",
            "answers": [
                "a little",
                "little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1113d8edf65c4e98801fa470743116c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "This material is superior ………………………….. that.",
            "description": "Use to after superior and inferior. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d43411773b5542f6828c8764c9d8053f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………………… of the four men.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare a person or thing with the group to which they/it belong(s).",
            "answers": [
                "the older",
                "oldest",
                "the oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc26e4097e914433b667345303dd6390"
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not earn as much as …………………………… does.",
            "description": "The subject form is used before a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ebe9562000742d78e6a796f5bc51357"
        },
        {
            "question": "A dog is ……………………………… than a cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more intelligent",
                "the more intelligent",
                "the most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e8e43c27ee9491d8154c00c0c9afa6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindi ………………………….. in many parts of India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is speaking",
                "spoken",
                "is spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0952c0ce4f7949e1b30dfcb117d81413"
        }
    ]
}